pheed.com 2012-01-11

# Pheed - Privacy Policy

Pheed Limited operates the Pheed website (the "Site") and related mobile applications and software (collectively with the Site, the "Service"). A premium service that enables people to subscribe to a particular ‘news feed’ and link to someone’s real life, in real time. Offering a selection of premium text, photo, voice note, audio content, video, link and other content (collectively, the “Content”). Pheed is committed to respecting and protecting your privacy. To that end, we have prepared this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") to describe our information gathering and dissemination practices and our data protection practices for the Service. The terms "Pheed," "we," "us," and "our" refer to Pheed Limited and its subsidiaries. The terms "you," "your," and "yours" refer to the user/customer utilizing the Service. This Privacy Policy is governed by our Terms of Use.

**Children**  
The Service is not intended for or directed to persons under the age of 13, and we will not knowingly collect information from such persons. Any person who provides information to us through registration or in any other manner on the Site or the Service represents to Pheed that they are 13 years of age or older. If we learn that a child under 13 has submitted personal information to us, we will attempt to delete the information as soon as possible. 

**Collection of Information**  
"Personally Identifiable Information" means any information which can be used to identify an individual, and may include, but is not limited to, name, email address, postal or other physical address, title, or occupation. We may collect the following Personally Identifiable Information from you when you register for or use the Service: name, email, phone number, credit card payment information, other payment information, and billing address. To participate in certain activities and to obtain certain services or documents offered on or through the Service, you may be asked to provide or share additional Personally Identifiable Information. We endeavor to limit our requests for Personally Identifiable Information to information we believe is reasonably necessary to achieve our purposes as described in the "Information Use" section below. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of the Service's features. Any Personally Identifiable Information received in communication or in material you transmit to Pheed by electronic mail or otherwise are and will be treated in accordance with our privacy policy. 

We also automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser, including without limitation your IP address, cookie information (as described below) and the page you request. 

**Cookies**  
Some of the pages on the Site may contain "cookies." A cookie is a small data file that may be sent to your Web browser and stored on your computer. This allows our server to "recognize" you when your computer visits the Site in the future. Most Web browsers can be configured to not accept cookies, or to notify you if a cookie is sent to you. In some instances, Pheed may collect non-Personally Identifiable Information (aggregate or demographic data) through cookies. 

**Information Use**  
Pheed uses Personally Identifiable Information for several general purposes: 

  * to provide you with product and service information, demos, and Service news,
  * to support the products and services offered on or through the Service,
  * to contact you on behalf of our content partners,
  * to contact you for feedback about products and services,
  * to fulfill your subscription requests,
  * to process your payments including credit checks and collection,
  * to notify you of technical updates or changes in policy, or
  * to contact you for marketing and promotional purposes.

We may use non-Personally Identifiable Information such as demographic data to analyze and develop our marketing strategy and further improve the Service and our products and services. 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**  
We will not sell or rent your Personally Identifiable Information to third parties except as described in this Privacy Policy. We may disclose your Personally Identifiable Information to other companies or people under any of the following circumstances: 

  * when we have your consent to share the information.
  * to those of our content providers or business partners from which you receive content and/or services (the “Providers”).
  * if sharing the information is reasonably necessary to provide a product or service that you have requested.
  * to keep you up to date on the latest Service announcements, special offers, or other information we think you would like to hear about either from us or from our partners.
  * if we believe in good faith that we are required to do so by law, in connection with litigation, to prevent a crime, or to protect personal safety, the public, or the Service.
  * in connection with a sale of stock or assets, reorganization, consolidation, merger with another entity, or if Pheed should ever file for bankruptcy or have its assets sold to another entity.
  * Pheed may also share non-Personally Identifiable Information, such as aggregate or demographic data, with third parties.

**Third Party Privacy Policies**  
As described in this Privacy Policy, Pheed may share your Personally Identifiable Information with our content Providers and/or business partners. Additionally, the Service may contain links to other sites. Pheed is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when leaving the Site or the Service to read the privacy statements of each site that collects Personally Identifiable Information. 

**Access**  
You may correct, amend, or delete your Personally Identifiable Information by editing your profile on the Site or emailing us at [support@pheed.com](mailto:support@pheed.com). 

**Security**  
We are committed to protecting Personally Identifiable Information from loss, misuse, disclosure, alteration, unauthorized access, and destruction. Pheed takes reasonable precautions to safeguard the confidentiality of Personally Identifiable Information. We protect the security of your Personally Identifiable Information during transmission to us by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts the information you input. While we strive to protect your Personally Identifiable Information, we cannot ensure the security of the information you transmit to us in all cases. 

**International Transfers**  
Personally Identifiable Information collected on or through the Service may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Pheed or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using the Service, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. 

**Your Consent to this Privacy Policy**  
By using this Service, you agree to this Privacy Policy. We may occasionally update this Privacy Policy. The date of the most recent update of this document will always be displayed at the beginning of this page. If we decide to use Personally Identifiable Information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users via email (the email address provided) or display a notice on the homepage. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy to stay informed about how we are protecting the Personally Identifiable Information we collect. Your continued use of this Service constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any updates. 

**Contacting Pheed**  
If you have any questions, comments, or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please email us at [support@pheed.com](mailto:support@pheed.com). 

Last Updated August 2011
